Pru results are also going to come today Varun,
tell me how will these numbers be, they may be a bit mixed,
Deep, now this is
because there is premium growth, no doubt there is
growth in profit as well, but the BNB
which we always see in every result,
this time
you may see some pressure on VNB margins, I will
put the numbers in front of you, net
premium income will increase by 3%, increase in AP by 3%,
profit may increase by 10-11%, it will
come around 245 crores, new business
premium is increasing by 14%, but
you may see a slight decline in the margins,
it may fall from 32% to around 29.5%,
so this is just a
matter of concern, keep an eye on BNB margins, even
if they come out well, then
I think it will be good for the insurance companies,
our estimate is
of a slight decline, you will see an increase of around 12-1.5% in AM, so
otherwise the growth is fine, keep an eye on VNB,
we are just talking about value  Of new business VNB
you have to keep an eye on this here, this will be a little important,
otherwise IC Pru is looking completely flat at this
time.